<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>HQ on Hugo Site</title>
    <link>https://remilarius.github.io/Anthology/command/</link>
    <description>Recent content in HQ on Hugo Site</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://remilarius.github.io/Anthology/command/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Daily List</title>
      <link>https://remilarius.github.io/Anthology/command/dailylist/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://remilarius.github.io/Anthology/command/dailylist/</guid>
      <description>Find Dentist  Weekday Errands: Get Nick and Dani to visit UC room
Saturday Errands: USPS, Morning
Move out: Saturday, Pack everything. Sunday, 12pm pick up. Go to Texas Roadhouse and other places. Drop stuff off at Stephon&amp;rsquo;s.
UC Storage Program Complaints
  Not accessible
  No insurance
  Find Adam a watch (Go to Swiss Watchmakes pass Felipe&amp;rsquo;s?)
  &amp;ldquo;If I loved you less, I might be able to talk about it more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Short List</title>
      <link>https://remilarius.github.io/Anthology/command/shortlist/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://remilarius.github.io/Anthology/command/shortlist/</guid>
      <description>BGS as an entity?
Cases:
Uncle: Employment Danjuan: Passport/AIDT Stamp Meidan: Verizon and Capitol One
Emails:
Contact Ben about drone equipment
Contact Rachel about nectar funding for bike
Major  Taxes for ad (set for next year, IT-201 plus 1040, plus education credits from Kevin)  SEAS  CAD Drill Bit Drawer Wrench Drawer  Summer Smorgasbord  CHEM S-1AB SEAS internship UC Interlock Animation Writing/World Building/Composing/Animating Build drone w/Kian and PS70 Documentation Other than Joy  To Do List  Create and update inventory spreadsheet for Adams HoCo Figure out Treasurer stuff for PRIMUS Get back on the UC stuff Attack Kian with drone Remember to apply for Boeing intership Jumpstart Interlock again, find program and funding  Define documentation for Stephon Define CAD engine for Saba File for Nectar funding    Summer To-Do List  Go to Primark w/Saba  More mundane to-do list  Figure out Amazon glitch w/Saba Email Katia about ES128 Do LSAT stuff w/Adam Train to beat up Adam  Misc  Susana&amp;rsquo;s Birthday (Aug 15), buy her a book.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Long List</title>
      <link>https://remilarius.github.io/Anthology/command/longlist/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://remilarius.github.io/Anthology/command/longlist/</guid>
      <description>Things coming up  Eat stuff w/Grace and her crew before classes start in the fall Explore places w/Kian at some point in semester Show Giulia around campus  Academic Stuff Saba&amp;rsquo;s spreadsheet
 Architecture? EC (EC10a/EC1010a/Ec1011a) or STAT (104/110) class?  Clubs  HRSFA/HAPIE Quidditch UC SEDS? PRIMUS HCEA/HCER? HURC? Archery IM Rep  Utilities/Bills  Pay off balances (11th of each month) Electricity/WiFi on auto Water (Remind mom to send before 20th of each month)  Payment Link Check Payment History Tango: $5.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Respond</title>
      <link>https://remilarius.github.io/Anthology/command/respond/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://remilarius.github.io/Anthology/command/respond/</guid>
      <description>Avery (Discord) David Vice (Phone call) Giulia (Text, ask for zoom call?) Madi (Before Jun.19) Jacob (Write letter) Stephon (Take a walk + finish letter) Thor (Discord) Dani (On Campus) Tramy and Havi (Facetime)   Rotation:
 Saba Lara BGS Grace  Ask Diego if the Unreal Engine can be used for animation
 Monday (Hollis) Tuesday (Susana, around 8pm) Wednesday (Work)  Insults for Adam:
&amp;ldquo;You can always be used as a bad example.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Protocols</title>
      <link>https://remilarius.github.io/Anthology/command/protocols/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://remilarius.github.io/Anthology/command/protocols/</guid>
      <description>General protocols  John Oliver on Monday evenings 20min Reddit/Facebook/Twitter/Youtube 30min allowance Reddit/Facebook/Twitter/Youtube, John Oliver on Monday evenings Call 1-2 people everyday, 30min-1hr on the bridge  When I stop breaking down my day, contact Leo because my scheduling system is broken.
Projects   Graduate college and maybe go to grad school  Write Magnum Opus UC Interlock Animation  Saba conditionals
 Don&amp;rsquo;t talk about her hair Don&amp;rsquo;t say slurs Don&amp;rsquo;t be stupid  Adam Conditionals</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
